Hello!
Today is the concert of Nako Okada.
It's at Kanagawa Kenmin Hall, isn't it?
I've never been to this place before.
I was wondering where in Kanagawa Prefecture it is.
I was wondering where in Kanagawa Prefecture it was, and then I found out that she was having a solo concert here.
LOL!
I looked up "Kashiwagi Yuki Solo Concert Kanagawa
It was the first thing that came up.
I had forgotten about it.
I can wear it next to Maho.
Indeed.
Don't let it erode.
You're right.
I'm gonna have to take it off a little bit.
I'll take care of the costumes.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to sing... with Nako.
We've got a lot going on.
I'll do my best for the whole day.
From the beginning, a thin rain rides through the night like a rainbow down in the sky, closing the window, that's my love
Two melodies in ambush
I couldn't stop.
And when I turned my head to look again
And there was the warm answer.
I'm sure the real answer's not out there
I'm sure you want me to give you the sadness right now
I know you want me to give it to you.
I don't think the answer's gone.
You can't do this anymore.
Give me nothing.
Next episode.
I believe in myself.
I don't know how much I can believe in my heart.
You and me, all the times we've been together.
I still can't believe I'm yours.
I'll lose it while I'm saying it.
lo seniiko eh?
I'm gonna kill you with tobacco.
I wrote a soccer cut.
Cut th...
Cut th... 4 Student.
Correct, Leif. And focus.
Thank you very much. I thought tomorrow would be good.
I don't have as much time as I thought I did after all that hard work.
I'm using the pink eyeshadow today.
I'm using it again today... but I want to put on my nails... but I don't know what they are... and I want to go to bed.
I haven't eaten... during the show.
Boo-boo... everyone, please give it your all for the next two and a half hours.
I'll get the money for the Gramophone.
I'm thinking...
Now all the time.
That's what it looks like.
I ask you.
Are you in love with someone who's in pain
or a delusional person?
Even when I think of it
I don't know what it means
what color would it be if you just nibbled on it
I don't know what it tastes like
I didn't even know the meaning of love, that flower
Our banana fruit
I'm sorry.
I've seen so many people wearing it.
I'm sure.
It's real.
Can you show us a picture?
Behind you.
Oh, I see.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
What's with this guy?
Interesting.
If you see this...
It's interesting.
Interesting.
He's your guy.
Hey, it's your man.
I don't care how much you love me... or how much I love you.Even though I'm loved so much, even though I love you so much
I can't help it, it's passing right in front of me
How I close my eyes and look at you
Because I want you so much
I want to see you so much, but I love you so much
Even the wind of love won't give it to me
I'm holding an umbrella, but your cheeks are giving it to me
I don't care
I can't do it, but it's not easy
I'm stepping on it, aren't I?
Yes, now for a moment, now for a moment
Yes, now for a moment
I want love
I can't sleep in the middle of the night
in my stupid dream
I turn on the TV
to drown it all out.
I started here.
I wanted to start from the beginning.
But I couldn't put on my makeup in time.
So I'll start from here.
When I jump on stage
I feel so good that I get an electric current.
It's in this sound.
The power of reason...
That's it, that's it, that's it...
I'll be working on it.
I'll do my best.
Okay, let's do it.
The hoop of reason.
Why don't you just run?
If you've eaten too much of their feelings...
If you can protect them emotionally
I bet I can't sleep like this
Yes, right now, for a moment
Yes, now for a moment
I can't sleep in the middle of the night
in my stupid dream
I turn on the TV
I'm drowning it all out
Thank you for watching
And everyone else.
Let's go all out!
Ladies and gentlemen...
Thank you very much for watching!
The part
Let's make something weird!
Hey!
Dasshin! Dasshin! Dasshin! Dasshin!
Let's make something weird
Hey!
Dasshin! Dasshin! Dasshin! Dasshin!
We just keep shining all night
You know we can make something
The photographer was filming us and listened to us while we were filming!
The photographer listened to us while we were filming
Thank you for your hard work
I'm sweating so much!
Luma sweat is so bad!
It was a great concert, wasn't it?
You've got a great voice, don't you?
It was nice to feel the warmth and enthusiasm of Naa-chan's fans.
Like the way you talked to Naa-chan at the end.
Only you can do that.
I was thinking about what I'm going to say when I graduate someday.
I didn't get a chance to watch it.
This was so precious.
For Na-chan's fans and AKB fans alike
I hope you can watch the video of today's concert.
Thanks for your hard work.
See you soon.
Thank you for watching!